upillar.com 2008-08-28

# uPillar.com | Privacy Policy

**[UPILLAR.COM](http://upillar.com/) (LEXON INDUSTRIES, INC.)**

## **Last Updated Date: September 19, 2007**

**1\. Acknowledgement and acceptance of terms**   

[Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) is a dba of Lexon Industries, Inc., a Nevada corporation. [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/), [Autopillar.com](http://autopillar.com/), [Rvpillar.com](http://rvpillar.com/), [Aircraftpillar.com](http://aircraftpillar.com/), [Cyclepillar.com](http://cyclepillar.com/), [Boatpillar.com](http://boatpillar.com/), are all part of Upillar.com’s website and are only shortcuts to their own location under Upillar.com’s website. All of these sites are governed by this Website Privacy Statement. [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Website Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/), you acknowledge and fully understand Upillar.com’s Website Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.  

**2\. Participating Merchant Policies**   

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

**3.** **Information We Collect and How We Use It**

[Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) collects certain information from and about its users four ways: directly from our Web Server logs, Web Beacons, the user, and with Cookies. 

**a. Web Server Logs.**

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include: 

  * Your Internet protocol address. 
  * The kind of browser or computer you use. 
  * Number of links you click within the site. 
  * State or country from which you accessed the site. 
  * Date and time of your visit. 
  * Name of your Internet service provider. 
  * Web page you linked to our site from. 
  * Pages you viewed on the site.
  * The amount of time you view each page.

**b. Web Beacons.**

Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We may include Web beacons on our web pages or emails in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information. 

**c. Use of Cookies.**

[Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.    

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.    

[Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value.    

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.  

**d. Personal Information Users.**

To help our customers with finding the classifieds that they are searching for, certain personal information is necessary to accomplish this task. Zip Codes, city, state, and other information may be necessary to bring the buyers and sellers together or to help the visitor or customer searching for a listing to find the right one nearest to him or her. Once a listing is found that you like, you may contact the user that posted this classified via email, phone, or letter depending on what means the seller has disclosed at the time of the listing. If an email is sent or “Offer” is made, [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) will provide the seller the necessary contact information that is needed for him or her to contact you. This may include, but is not limited to: your email, phone number, city, state, and Zip Code. This information will be sent to seller through email. Email is not always secure and may be viewable by other parties. We cannot guarantee that the seller will keep private this information. You agree that [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/), its parent and subsidiary companies, and its employees and agents will not be held liable for the release of this information. You give [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) the right to email you with this information if an offer is made to you (the seller) and/or question is made to you (the seller) from a potential buyer. Upon accepting these terms, you give [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) the right to release any information necessary in any situation that is needed or necessary to bring the buyers and sellers together.   

Further, you grant [Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) the right to disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties when necessary to:   

  * Protect ourselves from liability;
  * To respond to legal process or comply with law; or
  * In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

**4\. Accessing Web Account Information**   

[Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant at _[privacy@upillar.com](mailto:privacy@upillar.com)_   

**5\. Changes to this Statement**  

[Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.  

**6\. Waiver of Liability**  

[Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) will do everything in our powers to keep your personal information and financial information secure. Even with the best technology, some information may be intercepted, tracked, hacked, or discovered by unwanted people or programs. We assume no liability in the event that your information is discovered, found, hacked or stolen. ****  

**7\. Contacting Us**   

If you have questions regarding our Website Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at _[privacy@upillar.com](mailto:privacy@upillar.com)_ or mail your comments to:   

[Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/). 

**Attention: Privacy Statement Personal**

1071 East 100 South, Suite C-1

St. George, Utah 84770   

[Upillar.com](http://upillar.com/) will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.   

© 2007 Lexon Industries, Inc. All rights reserved.
